http://www.findlegalforms.com/xcart/customer/help.php?section=privacy

FindLegalForms.com Privacy Policy
Updated:
October 26, 2012
Our Privacy Policy applies to the following websites and services owned and operated by FindLegalForms, Inc.: FindLegalForms.com, FormTool.com, and FindLegalForms.com.s electronic signature service (.the FLF Signature Service.) (collectively referred to as "FindLegalForms").
FindLegalForms is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support of the responsible management of consumer information.
Consumer Information
During the process of delivering our content and information to you, we do not automatically collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, we do obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). This non-personally identifiable information collected by us is used for the purpose of analyzing our traffic.
When you i) purchase a form or subscription, ii) initiate a purchase of a form or subscription, or iii) initiate the electronic signing of a document from FindLegalForms , we may collect certain personal information to identify you and to assist you in your purchase or the electronic execution of an agreement.
We may use your email address to follow-up with you on a transaction on one of our sites that was initiated but not completed and to send you additional information about FindLegalForms and its products.
We will not disclose your personal information to third parties without your permission, except in the following circumstances: (i) to protect ourselves from liability; (ii) to respond to a legal process or comply with the law; (iii) to assist you in electronically signing a document as described below; and (iv) to process your payment as described below.
Electronic Signature Service
To effectively administer the FLF Signature Service, FindLegalForms may need to collect and disseminate personal information reasonably necessary to authenticate your identity (.Signature Service Information.).
Signature Service Information may include, although not limited to, your name, business title, personal address, business address, email address, time and date of signature, and internet protocol address.
In addition, when an individual or business (an .Initiating Signatory.) invites (shares with) another party to sign an agreement (an .Additional Signatory.), such Additional Signatory will also be asked to provide Signature Service Information. All of this information is recorded as part of the "transaction record" that is linked to the electronically signed document, and delivered to each signatory with the executed agreement.
By using the FLF Signature Service you are giving permission to share the Signature Service Information to all other participating signatories.
In connection with the electronic signing process, you will be asked to upload the relevant document to be signed (the .Transaction Document.).
This Transaction Document will be viewable and downloadable to all Additional Signatories.
In uploading the Transaction Document, you are giving permission to FindLegalForms to transmit this document to all participating signatories and store the document (as determined at the sole discretion of FindLegalForms). In addition, the FindLegalForms administrators have access, for purposes of site administration only, to the Transaction Document.
FindLegalForms expressly agrees with respect to the Transaction Document to respect and protect the confidentiality of any confidential client information, lawyer-client or attorney-client privileged information contained in the Transaction Document. Other than as indicated above, we will not disclose the Transaction Document to third parties without your permission except to respond to a legal process or comply with the law.
Credit Card and Payment Processors
Our Credit Card and Payment Processors may also collect information from you in order to be able to process your payments.
Cookies
Our sites, as well as most sites on the Internet, use cookies to enhance your experience on the web. Generally, we cannot use these cookies to personally identify you in any way. The only time we can use cookies to personally identify you is when you choose to enable cookie identification. We use cookies to enhance your experience and enjoyment of our sites. We also use cookies to allow transactions, such as form purchases, to take place as well as to allow users to login into accounts on the sites. While we believe that cookies enhance your Internet experience, they are not required to simply browse our sites.
Although we don't recommend doing so on our sites, if you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information.
Consent to Transferring and Processing of Data in the United States
By using FindLegalForms, you consent to having your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.
For users in England and Wales, the information you provide to FindLegalForms is also subject to the Data Protection Act 1998. You have a right of access under data protection legislation to the personal data that we hold about you.
Modification of Policy
FindLegalForms may modify this privacy policy at any time without prior notice. Continued use of FindLegalForms following any change constitutes your acceptance of the change. We therefore ask you to review this privacy policy occasionally to ensure that you are aware of the most recent version.
Platform for Privacy Preferences
FindLegalForms supports P3P, the Platform for Privacy Preferences, allowing us to convey our privacy policies, to the extent possible, in standardized, machine-readable code. While our site supports P3P, the resulting code has inherent limitations such that it may not completely and accurately express all of our data practices. Some P3P-enabled browsers may interpret the same P3P code in different ways, while others may interpret P3P code in a manner inconsistent with the original intention. Accordingly, your browser's interpretation of the P3P code should only be considered as a short-hand expression of our privacy practices. This Privacy Policy remains our primary policy, and takes precedence over the P3P code for all purposes.
If you have any additional questions or concerns about our dedication to consumer privacy, please do not hesitate to contact us.
Attorney prepared
Our forms are kept up-to-date and accurate by our lawyers
Unlike other sites, every document on FindLegalForms.com is prepared by an attorney, so you can be sure that you are getting a form that is accurate and valid in your state.
Valid in your state
Our forms are guaranteedto be valid in your state
Our team works tirelessly to keep our products current. As the laws change in your state, so do our forms.
Over 1,300,000satisfied customers
In over 10 years of creating and selling legal forms, our focus has never changed: providing our customers high quality legal products, low prices and an experience that takes some confusion out of the law.
Free eSignature
Sign your form online, free with any form purchase
We now provide a free Electronic Signature Service to all of our visitors.
There are no hidden charges or subscription fees, it's just plain free.
60-Days Money Back
Try our forms with no risk
If you are unhappy with your form purchase for any reason at all, contact us within 60 days and we will refund 100% of your money back.
Instant download
Download your form ina format you can use
After you place your order, your forms will be available for immediate download.
You can save the file for later use or print it immediately. We make all formats available to you at no extra charge.
